Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Annual Conference records, 1908-2004
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Annual Conference records, 1908-2004
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Annual Conference records, 1908-2004
24-04-3387
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine
1.5 cubic ft.
Programs, proceedings, news clippings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Programs, proceedings, news clippings associated with the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Annual Conference for Veterinarians.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Annual Conference for Veterinarians began in 1909 when the college was still known as the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine. The purpose of the conference was and is continuing education for veterinarians in New York State.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Programs, proceedings, news clippings associated with the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Annual Conference for Veterinarians.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine; Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine
Subjects:
Veterinary medicine--Study and Teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Programs, 1908-1915 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Programs, 1916-1920 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Programs, 1921-1925 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Programs, 1926-1930 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Programs, 1931-1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Programs, 1936-1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Programs, 1941-1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Programs, 1946-1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Programs, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Programs, 1956-1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Programs, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Programs, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Programs, 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Programs, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Programs, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Programs, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Programs, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Programs, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Programs for Spouses, 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Programs for Spouses, 1980-1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Program of Clinics and Demonstrations, 1933-1955 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Abstracts, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Abstracts, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Abstracts, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Abstracts, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Abstracts, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Abstracts, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Abstracts, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Abstracts, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Proceedings, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Proceedings, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Proceedings, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Proceedings, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Proceedings, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Clippings - 19th, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Clippings - 27th, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Clippings - 31st, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Clippings - 32nd, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Clippings - 33rd, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Clippings - 34th, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Clippings - 35th, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Clippings - 36th, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Clippings - 37th, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Clippings - 39th, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Clippings - 40th, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Clippings - 45th, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Clippings - 46th, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Clippings - 47th, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Clippings - 48th, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Clippings - 50th, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Clippings - 51st, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Clippings - 52nd, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Clippings - 53rd, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Clippings - 55th, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Clippings - undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Register, 1909-1916 (Box 4)
- Register, 1917-1937 (Box 4)
- Register, 1938-1949 (Box 4)
- Register, 1950-1952 (Box 5)